http://www.wackyuses.com/privacy.html

CONTACT
We respect your privacy.
Wacky Uses firmly believes in your right to privacy. This website does NOT collect anonymous data through the use of cookies.
No information is sold or released to anyone about visitors to this site without prior consent. This includes e-mail registration to mailing lists, or information requests. You, as a visitor of this web site, are not required to supply any personal information unless you decide to fill out online forms (signing up for our free newsletter to the right), or submit an email to employees or departments at WackyUses.
We use Google as a third-party vendor to serve ads when you visit our website. Google uses the DoubleClick DART cookie and may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like to opt out of the use of the DART cookie, click here.
WackyUses does not attempt to collect personal information from children. If children do send personal information, such as sending e-mail, filling out online forms, etc., the information is deleted. Note that WackyUses cannot always determine that a user is a child.
WackyUses does generate aggregate reports regarding the number of visitors to this web site. These reports do not contain any personally identifiable information.
When you visit any Internet site, your unique address (known as an "IP address") is recorded. WackyUses does not and will not release any information about the collection of this address to any third party except under court order. WackyUses archives the log files in order to create aggregate statistical reports, detect errors at the web site, and for security reasons. The log files are eventually deleted.
Give Your
Kid a Book
Just for Laughs.
Available Now
Order Your Copy Now!
Clean It!
Fix It!Eat It!
Marx & Lennon:
The Parallel Sayings
You Know You’ve
Reached Middle Age If...
You Know You
Need a Vacation If...
Copyright © 1995-2020 Joey Green. All rights reserved. Privacy Policy.
